# ony Carbone

💌 anthonydavidcarbone@gmail.com | 🧩 anthonycarbone.github.io | 🗘 anthonycarbone | 🛅 ancarb | 💆 @\_anthonycarbone

## Summary.

Third year Aerospace Engineering and Advanced Physics student with an avid interest in serving Australia's developing space industry. I am a multidisciplinary creative who makes sure to be exposed to and employ a diverse range of technologies in my projects and studies. I have experience in robotics, electrical and mechatronic subsystem design, web development, academic research, and as a glider pilot. I hope to expand to spacebased technologies, space operations, machine learning, and software development.

**Programming** 















Software











# **Experience**



#### **International Centre for Radio Astronomy Research**

Nov. 2020 - Feb. 2021

SUMMER INTERN

Investigated applying the JPEG2000 based webjpip.js library to remotely viewing very large image radio astronomy spectral data cubes.

• Presented recommendations to AusSRC for development of webjpip is as a viable product for future SKA use.

#### **Autonomous Vehicle Competition - ENGG1000**

Feb. 2019 - Mar. 2019

• Lead a team of 6 first-year students to win the courses' internal track competition.

- Programmed the autonomous robot in Arduino (C/C++).
- Applied small motors, laser-cut gears, and servos.
- Designed and built an effective power distribution system with a 3s LiPO battery and Veroboard.

#### Warman Design & Build Competition, UNSW Qualifier

TEAM LEAD

May. 2019 - Sep. 2019

• Worked in a team of 6 to qualify to represent UNSW at the global competition in parallel with studies.

· Designed and built powerful servo and motor subsystems, and an effective power distribution system with two 3s LiPO batteries.

**Gliding Club of WA** 

AWARDED MOST ADVANCED BEGINNER PILOT

2018 - 2019

**International Astronautical Congress** 

STUDENT ATTENDEE

Sep. 2017

**United Space School** 

• Planned and presented a theoretical mission to Mars in a team of 40 international students.

• Awarded a flown Texas flag for extraordinary achievement, only five were awarded.

#### Education



### **University of New South Wales**

AEROSPACE ENGINEERING (HONS) · ADVANCED PHYSICS (HONS)

Feb. 2019 - 2024

84 average mark Dean's Honours List, UNSW Engineering School

**Trinity College** 

WESTERN AUSTRALIAN CERTIFICATE OF EDUCATION

• 99.60 ATAR | Head of Year 12 Award | Top student in state for Aviation ATAR

Jul. 2014 - Nov. 2018

### Interests



#### Volunteer.

#### **Edmund Rice Camps WA/NSW**

Jul. 2017 - Present

VOLUNTEER LEADER

**UNSW Hall** HOUSE PRESIDENT

## **UNSW Mechanical Engineering Students Society**

SECRETARY, FIRST & THIRD YEAR REPS

Mar. 2019 - Present

# References Available Upon Request\_

